p1 = [
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "bd", "osnova2": "ti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "b", "osnova2": "l", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "b", "osnova2": "s", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "bil", "osnova2": "žnica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "b", "osnova2": "logorica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "b", "osnova2": "žati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "bl", "osnova2": "d", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "br", "osnova2": "g", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "c", "osnova2": "na", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "c", "osnova2": "pljenje", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "c", "osnova2": "lina", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "c", "osnova2": "pivo", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "cr", "osnova2": "vo", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "cv", "osnova2": "će", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "cv", "osnova2": "t", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "cv", "osnova2": "tača", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "čov", "osnova2": "k", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "d", "osnova2": "liti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "d", "osnova2": "ljenje", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "d", "osnova2": "te", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "d", "osnova2": "ca", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "d", "osnova2": "čak", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "d", "osnova2": "čji", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "d", "osnova2": "d", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "d", "osnova2": "litelj", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "d", "osnova2": "lo", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "d", "osnova2": "l", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "d", "osnova2": "ljiv", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "d", "osnova2": "telina", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "d", "osnova2": "tinjstvo", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "d", "osnova2": "vojčica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "d", "osnova2": "vojka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "dol", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "dvos", "osnova2": "d", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "gluhon", "osnova2": "m", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "gluhosl", "osnova2": "p", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "gn", "osnova2": "zdo", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "gor", "osnova2": "ti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "grabl", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "gr", "osnova2": "h", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "grobl", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "gus", "osnova2": "nica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "inžen", "osnova2": "r", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "inžen", "osnova2": "rka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "in", "osnova2": "kcija", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "jan", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "kasn", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "kl", "osnova2": "šta", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "kol", "osnova2": "vka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "kor", "osnova2": "n", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "kral", "osnova2": "vstvo", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "kral", "osnova2": "žnica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "kukur", "osnova2": "k", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "let", "osnova2": "lica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "let", "osnova2": "ti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "l", "osnova2": "čiti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "l", "osnova2": "čnica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "l", "osnova2": "čnik", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "l", "osnova2": "gati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "l", "osnova2": "k", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "l", "osnova2": "n", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "l", "osnova2": "p", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "l", "osnova2": "piti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "l", "osnova2": "s", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "l", "osnova2": "ska", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "l", "osnova2": "vati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "l", "osnova2": "vo", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "l", "osnova2": "karnica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "l", "osnova2": "karnik", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "l", "osnova2": "pilo", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "l", "osnova2": "pota", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "l", "osnova2": "stve", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "l", "osnova2": "šnjak", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "l", "osnova2": "to", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "l", "osnova2": "tovati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "l", "osnova2": "vak", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "l", "osnova2": "vakinja", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "medv", "osnova2": "d", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "m", "osnova2": "njati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "m", "osnova2": "šati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "mišl", "osnova2": "n", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "m", "osnova2": "riti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "m", "osnova2": "sec", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "m", "osnova2": "sečina", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "m", "osnova2": "sto", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "ml", "osnova2": "ko", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "nam", "osnova2": "štaj", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "napr", "osnova2": "d", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "nat", "osnova2": "can", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "nat", "osnova2": "catelj", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "nat", "osnova2": "cateljica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "nat", "osnova2": "čaj", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "ned", "osnova2": "lja", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "nevr", "osnova2": "me", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "n", "osnova2": "kati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "n", "osnova2": "m", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "n", "osnova2": "mački", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "n", "osnova2": "žan", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "obav", "osnova2": "st", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "ob", "osnova2": "d", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "ob", "osnova2": "siti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "oc", "osnova2": "na", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "od", "osnova2": "lo", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "od", "osnova2": "vati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "od", "osnova2": "ća", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "od", "osnova2": "l", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "od", "osnova2": "nuti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "ogr", "osnova2": "v", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "om", "osnova2": "r", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "oruž", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "os", "osnova2": "ćaj", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "os", "osnova2": "ćati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "os", "osnova2": "t", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "os", "osnova2": "tilo", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "osm", "osnova2": "h", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "ozl", "osnova2": "da", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "pac", "osnova2": "nt", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "pac", "osnova2": "ntica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "p", "osnova2": "sak", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "p", "osnova2": "tao", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "p", "osnova2": "sma", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "p", "osnova2": "smarica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "p", "osnova2": "snik", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "p", "osnova2": "snikinja", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "p", "osnova2": "šak", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "p", "osnova2": "šakinja", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "p", "osnova2": "ščanik", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "p", "osnova2": "vač", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "p", "osnova2": "vačica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "p", "osnova2": "vati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "pob", "osnova2": "da", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "podr", "osnova2": "tlo", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "po", "osnova2": "sti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "poned", "osnova2": "ljak", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "pos", "osnova2": "ćivati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "pos", "osnova2": "t", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "pos", "osnova2": "titi", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "posl", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "posl", "osnova2": "podne", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "posl", "osnova2": "dnji", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "pov", "osnova2": "st", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "pov", "osnova2": "ren", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "prad", "osnova2": "d", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "preds", "osnova2": "dnica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "preds", "osnova2": "dnik", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "predsobl", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "prem", "osnova2": "stiti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "prem", "osnova2": "štati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "pr", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "pr", "osnova2": "laz", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "pr", "osnova2": "nos", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "pr", "osnova2": "podne", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "pr", "osnova2": "titi", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "pr", "osnova2": "voz", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "prim", "osnova2": "r", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "primor", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "pripov", "osnova2": "tka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "prizeml", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "priznan", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "prol", "osnova2": "će", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "prom", "osnova2": "na", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "ran", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "ran", "osnova2": "nica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "ran", "osnova2": "nik", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "raskriž", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "razum", "osnova2": "ti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "redosl", "osnova2": "d", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "r", "osnova2": "č", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "r", "osnova2": "dak", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "r", "osnova2": "ka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "r", "osnova2": "šiti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "r", "osnova2": "čnik", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "r", "osnova2": "šavati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "r", "osnova2": "šen", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "rubl", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "sav", "osnova2": "t", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "s", "osnova2": "čanj", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "s", "osnova2": "cište", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "s", "osnova2": "ćati se", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "s", "osnova2": "ći", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "s", "osnova2": "dalo", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "s", "osnova2": "dati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "s", "osnova2": "diti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "s", "osnova2": "kira", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "s", "osnova2": "me", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "s", "osnova2": "menka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "s", "osnova2": "na", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "s", "osnova2": "sti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "s", "osnova2": "titi se", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "s", "osnova2": "ver", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "s", "osnova2": "veroistok", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "s", "osnova2": "verozapad", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "sl", "osnova2": "p", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "sm", "osnova2": "h", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "sm", "osnova2": "šak", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "sm", "osnova2": "r", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "sm", "osnova2": "ti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "sn", "osnova2": "g", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "sn", "osnova2": "žiti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "sn", "osnova2": "gović", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "sn", "osnova2": "žan", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "spr", "osnova2": "da", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "sr", "osnova2": "da", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "stan", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "st", "osnova2": "g", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "st", "osnova2": "na", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "stol", "osnova2": "će", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "sus", "osnova2": "d", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "sus", "osnova2": "da", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "sus", "osnova2": "dstvo", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "susn", "osnova2": "žica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "sv", "osnova2": "ća", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "sv", "osnova2": "t", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "sv", "osnova2": "tliti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "sv", "osnova2": "tiljka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "sv", "osnova2": "tionik", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "sv", "osnova2": "tlo", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "šted", "osnova2": "ti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "šut", "osnova2": "ti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "t", "osnova2": "lo", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "T", "osnova2": "lovo", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "t", "osnova2": "sto", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "t", "osnova2": "dan", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "t", "osnova2": "me", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "t", "osnova2": "rati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "t", "osnova2": "stenina", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "toplom", "osnova2": "r", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "tra", "osnova2": "kt", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "tros", "osnova2": "d", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "ugl", "osnova2": "n", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "ul", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "uman", "osnova2": "nik", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "umirovl", "osnova2": "nica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "umirovl", "osnova2": "nik", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "um", "osnova2": "tnica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "um", "osnova2": "tnik", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "um", "osnova2": "tnost", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "upotr", "osnova2": "biti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "usp", "osnova2": "h", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "vesel", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "vid", "osnova2": "ti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "v", "osnova2": "nac", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "v", "osnova2": "st", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "vis", "osnova2": "ti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "v", "osnova2": "čnost", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "v", "osnova2": "nčan", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "v", "osnova2": "nčati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "v", "osnova2": "ra", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "v", "osnova2": "rnica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "v", "osnova2": "rnik", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "v", "osnova2": "ronauk", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "v", "osnova2": "roučitelj", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "v", "osnova2": "roučiteljica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "v", "osnova2": "rovati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "v", "osnova2": "snik", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "v", "osnova2": "šalica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "v", "osnova2": "štica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "v", "osnova2": "ština", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "v", "osnova2": "tar", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "v", "osnova2": "trovit", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "v", "osnova2": "verica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "v", "osnova2": "žba", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "v", "osnova2": "žbati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "v", "osnova2": "žbenica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "vol", "osnova2": "ti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "vr", "osnova2": "me", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "vrt", "osnova2": "ti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "za", "osnova2": "dnica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "za", "osnova2": "dnički", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "zal", "osnova2": "v", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "zam", "osnova2": "na", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "zapov", "osnova2": "d", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "zav", "osnova2": "sa", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "zd", "osnova2": "la", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "z", "osnova2": "vati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "zv", "osnova2": "r", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["ije", "je"], "osnova": "zv", "osnova2": "zda", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "žel", "osnova2": "znica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "žel", "osnova2": "zo", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "ije/je", "correctAnswer": ["je", "ije"], "osnova": "živ", "osnova2": "ti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
]

p2 = [
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "automehani", "osnova2": "ar", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "automehani", "osnova2": "arka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "cvjeta", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "cvr", "osnova2": "ak", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "aj", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "amac", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "arapa", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "aroban", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "arobnica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "arobnjak", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "as", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "asopis", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "aša", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "avao", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "ekaonica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "ekati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "ekić", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "elo", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "empres", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "estitka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "esto", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "ešalj", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "ešnjak", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "etiri", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "etka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "etkica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "etrdeset", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "etrnaest", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "etverokratnik", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "etverokut", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "etvorka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "etvrtak", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "etvrti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "etvrtina", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "i", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "inele", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "initi", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "ist", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "ista", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "ista", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "istiti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "itanka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "itaonica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "itati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "itav", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "izma", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "okolada", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "ovjek", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "u", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "u", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "uditi se", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "udo", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "uti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "uvati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "vrst", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "ćevap", "osnova2": "ić", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "de", "osnova2": "ko", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "dje", "osnova2": "ak", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "dje", "osnova2": "ji", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "djevoj", "osnova2": "ica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "doru", "osnova2": "ak", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "druk", "osnova2": "iji", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "dvoto", "osnova2": "ka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "gimnasti", "osnova2": "ar", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "gimnasti", "osnova2": "arka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "gla", "osnova2": "alo", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "hla", "osnova2": "e", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "igra", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "igra", "osnova2": "ica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "igra", "osnova2": "ka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "ispri", "osnova2": "ati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "ispri", "osnova2": "avati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "ispri", "osnova2": "nica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "ivan", "osnova2": "ica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "ju", "osnova2": "er", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "kle", "osnova2": "ati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "klju", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "knjižni", "osnova2": "ar", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "knjižni", "osnova2": "arka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "kola", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "koli", "osnova2": "ina", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "koli", "osnova2": "nik", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "kornja", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "kota", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "kov", "osnova2": "eg", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "krma", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "kroja", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "kroja", "osnova2": "ica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "lije", "osnova2": "iti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "lije", "osnova2": "nica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "lije", "osnova2": "nik", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "lopo", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "ljubi", "osnova2": "ast", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "ljulja", "osnova2": "ka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "ma", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "ma", "osnova2": "ak", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "ma", "osnova2": "ić", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "ma", "osnova2": "ka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "mađioni", "osnova2": "ar", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "mađioni", "osnova2": "arka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "masla", "osnova2": "ak", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "matemati", "osnova2": "ar", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "matemati", "osnova2": "arka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "mehani", "osnova2": "ar", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "mehani", "osnova2": "arka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "mjese", "osnova2": "ina", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "mladun", "osnova2": "e", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "mom", "osnova2": "ad", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "mu", "osnova2": "iti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "na", "osnova2": "in", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "nao", "osnova2": "ale", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "naran", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "naru", "osnova2": "iti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "naru", "osnova2": "ivati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "naslonja", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "natika", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "natje", "osnova2": "aj", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "nau", "osnova2": "iti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "nepuša", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "nepuša", "osnova2": "ica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "nov", "osnova2": "anica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "nov", "osnova2": "anik", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "novorođen", "osnova2": "e", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "njema", "osnova2": "ki", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "obla", "osnova2": "an", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "obla", "osnova2": "iti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "o", "osnova2": "uh", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "odli", "osnova2": "an", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "odlu", "osnova2": "iti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "odlu", "osnova2": "ivati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "ogrta", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "otklju", "osnova2": "ati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "otklju", "osnova2": "avati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "pala", "osnova2": "inka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "papu", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "pau", "osnova2": "ina", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "p", "osnova2": "ela", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "pisa", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "pješ", "osnova2": "anik", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "pjeva", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "pjeva", "osnova2": "ica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "pla", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "plesa", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "plesa", "osnova2": "ica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "pliva", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "pliva", "osnova2": "ica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "plo", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "plo", "osnova2": "nik", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "po", "osnova2": "etak", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "po", "osnova2": "etnica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "podru", "osnova2": "je", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "pokaziva", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "pokriva", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "politi", "osnova2": "ar", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "politi", "osnova2": "arka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "pre", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "presko", "osnova2": "iti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "pri", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "pri", "osnova2": "ati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "pri", "osnova2": "est", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "pro", "osnova2": "itati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "prodava", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "prodava", "osnova2": "ica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "puša", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "puša", "osnova2": "ica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "ra", "osnova2": "un", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "ra", "osnova2": "unalo", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "raj", "osnova2": "ica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "razli", "osnova2": "it", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "re", "osnova2": "enica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "rije", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "rje", "osnova2": "nik", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "ru", "osnova2": "ak", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "ru", "osnova2": "ati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "ru", "osnova2": "e", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "ru", "osnova2": "nik", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "rup", "osnova2": "ić", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "ruži", "osnova2": "ast", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "savija", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "sendvi", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "sestri", "osnova2": "na", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "sije", "osnova2": "anj", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "sko", "osnova2": "iti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "slasti", "osnova2": "arnica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "sli", "osnova2": "an", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "slu", "osnova2": "aj", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "slu", "osnova2": "ajnost", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "sto", "osnova2": "ar", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "sto", "osnova2": "arica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "strunja", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "sun", "osnova2": "an", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "svira", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "svira", "osnova2": "ica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "te", "osnova2": "aj", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "tenisa", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "tenisa", "osnova2": "ica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "to", "osnova2": "ka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "tra", "osnova2": "nica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "tratin", "osnova2": "ica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "tr", "osnova2": "ati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "u", "osnova2": "enica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "u", "osnova2": "enik", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "u", "osnova2": "enje", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "u", "osnova2": "initi", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "u", "osnova2": "ionica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "u", "osnova2": "itelj", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "u", "osnova2": "iteljica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "u", "osnova2": "iti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "uklju", "osnova2": "iti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "uklju", "osnova2": "ivati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "usisava", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "uskli", "osnova2": "nik", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "uspinja", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "ve", "osnova2": "er", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "ve", "osnova2": "era", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "ve", "osnova2": "erati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "velja", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "vesla", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "vesla", "osnova2": "ica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "violon", "osnova2": "elist", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "violon", "osnova2": "elistica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "violon", "osnova2": "elo", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "vje", "osnova2": "nost", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "vjen", "osnova2": "anje", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "vjen", "osnova2": "ati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "vjerou", "osnova2": "itelj", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "vjerou", "osnova2": "iteljica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "vodi", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "vodi", "osnova2": "ica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "voza", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "voza", "osnova2": "ica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "zajedni", "osnova2": "ki", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "zaklju", "osnova2": "ak", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "zavi", "osnova2": "aj", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "zna", "osnova2": "iti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "zna", "osnova2": "ka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "ži", "osnova2": "ara", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "bi", "osnova2": "e", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "Boži", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "boži", "osnova2": "ni", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "bra", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "brati", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "budu", "osnova2": "nost", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "cvije", "osnova2": "e", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "ekić", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "elav", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "ćevap", "osnova2": "ić", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "irilica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "uk", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "up", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "do", "osnova2": "i", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "doma", "osnova2": "i", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "doma", "osnova2": "ica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "doma", "osnova2": "in", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "došaš", "osnova2": "e", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "drve", "osnova2": "e", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "du", "osnova2": "an", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "ga", "osnova2": "e", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "goš", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "i", "osnova2": "i", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "ispe", "osnova2": "i", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "iza", "osnova2": "i", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "izi", "osnova2": "i", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "k", "osnova2": "i", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "kozli", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "krš", "osnova2": "anin", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "krš", "osnova2": "anka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "ku", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "le", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "le", "osnova2": "i", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "liš", "osnova2": "e", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "ma", "osnova2": "ić", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "ma", "osnova2": "eha", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "ma", "osnova2": "uhica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "miši", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "mladi", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "mo", "osnova2": "i", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "mogu", "osnova2": "nost", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "na", "osnova2": "i", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "ne", "osnova2": "ak", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "ne", "osnova2": "akinja", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "nesre", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "no", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "no", "osnova2": "ni", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "obu", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "obu", "osnova2": "i", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "odje", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "omogu", "osnova2": "avati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "omogu", "osnova2": "iti", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "omogu", "osnova2": "ivati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "osje", "osnova2": "aj", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "osje", "osnova2": "ati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "oti", "osnova2": "i", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "pam", "osnova2": "enje", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "pe", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "pe", "osnova2": "i", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "pi", "osnova2": "e", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "pla", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "pla", "osnova2": "ati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "plu", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "polno", "osnova2": "ka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "pomo", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "pomo", "osnova2": "i", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "pono", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "posje", "osnova2": "ivati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "pove", "osnova2": "alo", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "povr", "osnova2": "e", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "pro", "osnova2": "i", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "prolje", "osnova2": "e", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "ražnji", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "re", "osnova2": "i", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["č", "ć"], "osnova": "rup", "osnova2": "ić", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "si", "osnova2": "i", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "sje", "osnova2": "ati se", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "sje", "osnova2": "i", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "sme", "osnova2": "e", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "snjegovi", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "spava", "osnova2": "ica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "sre", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "srnda", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "staja", "osnova2": "ica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "sti", "osnova2": "i", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "stolje", "osnova2": "e", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "sve", "osnova2": "enik", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "svije", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "svu", "osnova2": "i", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "še", "osnova2": "er", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "štapi", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "te", "osnova2": "i", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "teku", "osnova2": "ica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "teku", "osnova2": "ina", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "tisu", "osnova2": "u", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "tre", "osnova2": "i", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "tre", "osnova2": "ina", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "trudno", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "tu", "osnova2": "i", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "u", "osnova2": "i", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "uš", "osnova2": "e", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "vo", "osnova2": "e", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "vo", "osnova2": "ka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "vo", "osnova2": "njak", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "vra", "osnova2": "ati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "vre", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "vrti", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "vru", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "vru", "osnova2": "ica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "vru", "osnova2": "ina", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "vu", "osnova2": "i", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "č/ć", "correctAnswer": ["ć", "č"], "osnova": "zada", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
]

p3 = [
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["dž", "đ"], "osnova": "deter", "osnova2": "ent", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["dž", "đ"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "amija", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["dž", "đ"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "em", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["dž", "đ"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "emper", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["dž", "đ"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "ep", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["dž", "đ"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "eparac", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["dž", "đ"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "ungla", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["dž", "đ"], "osnova": "ho", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["dž", "đ"], "osnova": "naru", "osnova2": "ba", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["dž", "đ"], "osnova": "pan", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["dž", "đ"], "osnova": "pi", "osnova2": "ama", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["dž", "đ"], "osnova": "u", "osnova2": "benik", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "an", "osnova2": "eo", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "doga", "osnova2": "aj", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "doga", "osnova2": "ati se", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "ak", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "avao", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "", "osnova2": "ur", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "gospo", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "gospo", "osnova2": "ica", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "gra", "osnova2": "evina", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "grož", "osnova2": "e", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "izme", "osnova2": "u", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "kra", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "le", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "ma", "osnova2": "ioničar", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "ma", "osnova2": "ioničarka", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "me", "osnova2": "u", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "novoro", "osnova2": "enče", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "odre", "osnova2": "ivati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "oru", "osnova2": "e", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "poga", "osnova2": "ati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "poro", "osnova2": "aj", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "posu", "osnova2": "e", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "posu", "osnova2": "ivati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "ro", "osnova2": "ak", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "ro", "osnova2": "akinja", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "ro", "osnova2": "endan", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "ro", "osnova2": "enje", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "sme", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "strojovo", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "sva", "osnova2": "a", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "tu", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "tvr", "osnova2": "ava", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "ure", "osnova2": "aj", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "ure", "osnova2": "ivati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "uspore", "osnova2": "ivati", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
    { "question": "popuni", "hint": "dž/đ", "correctAnswer": ["đ", "dž"], "osnova": "že", "osnova2": "", "glagol": "", "pin": "", },
]